Paulo Bezerra

Support Analyst PL at EY

Email: pauloh2012sul@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://phbrazil.github.io/PauloBezerra/

Experienced Support Analyst with a demonstrated history of working in the accounting industry. Highly skilled specially in MS Excel focusing in creation and automation of performance reports. Skilled also in Windows, Java programming, OS X, Operations Management, Microsoft Excel, IT Service Management, VBA, SQL, ETL, Dashboards creation and Systems Implementation. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor's Degree focused in Computer Systems Analysis from Senac São Paulo.

Experience

EY

JUNE 2014 - Current

Support Analyst

• Solid knowledge in Microsoft Excel, VBA, ETL and Performance Indicators. • Responsible for create and maintain the operational KPIs reports generated daily and presented to the lead using his automatic templates. • Paulo created internal tools developed in Java to decrease the call time during the Support. • Provide remote assistance (Phone, Chat and Email) mainly to EY Brazil internal and external customers, performed in Portuguese and English languages; • Troubleshooting problems related to internal software, operating systems, email applications, office tools, network connectivity and telephony; • Tickets escalation for several global teams using ITIL methodology; • Participation in projects to improve processes in Service Desk area, automatizing internal process, working together with other teams to minimize the impact of new deployments.

Nestle S.A.

OCTOBER 2013 - MAY 2014 (8 MONTHS)

Service Desk Analyst

Paulo worked as Bilingual Remote Support Analyst in MS Windows Vista and Windows 7 platforms. He provided support in systems as AS400, SAP(Module FI and CO), Checkpoint, Active Directory, BitLocker, Mercury and other applications using the HP Service Manager;

Flash Courier

NOVEMBER 2008 - OCTOBER 2014 (5 YEARS)

Deployment Analyst

Paulo worked for five years as Implementation Analyst, System Tester and Project Manager in a logistic company. His main roles were create Project Scopes and Algorithms for new clients and new tools, defining metrics and layouts, creating internal and external SLA's reports models with customers , partners and vendors, participating in the Business decisions as IT member consultant, analyzing and creating reports and assisting from the beginning of new projects to the deployment.

Deloitte

OCTOBER 2006 - JULY 2008 (1 YEAR 10 MONTHS)

Administrative Assistant

Paulo started his career as Administrative Assistant trainee at Deloitte when he was
16. He worked for about two years assisting in administrative routines in audit firm's
office.

Education

Senac São Paulo

2017 - 2019

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Systems Analysis, Bachelor's Degree, Computer Systems Analysis, 2017 - 2019